[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 3, "question": "What's rude sex?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 4, "answer": "Well, you don't want me to tell you on this show.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "But really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "Yes, you go hair spray, a little something.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "Michele Bachmann, Sarah Palin -- what do you make of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "I don't make a lot of them.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michele Bachmann", "Sarah Palin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "Whereas you have the Tea Party who are gathering the momentum, have a huge following behind them, where there's Rick Perry or Michele Bachmann or whatever, but there is still a sense of what would we be getting ourselves into if they actually governed the country?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "WP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "EX", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "JJR", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VB", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "But you know what's so interesting about our politics in this country is you are what you looked like.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick Perry", "Michele Bachmann"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 80, "question": "What do you think of Barack Obama's performance?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 81, "answer": "I'm not happy with it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "VBP", ",", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "How long have you lived in America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "I live here, oh, over 20 years.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "You love it, don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "I do love it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["London"]}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 116, "question": "But you're very much an L.A. girl, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 117, "answer": "I love London.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["L.A."]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "And all of the big stars tend to live here, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marlon Brando"]}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 133, "question": "Marlon Brandon?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "Yes, Marlon Brando was fantastic.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "Give me a little taste of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "Did you grasp why a man would behave like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "Who knows?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "You're on Twitter all the time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "Can you imagine doing something like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "Can you imagine standing in front of a mirror and photographing yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "I personally wouldn't have communication with people I didn't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "Does it matter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "I think it matters.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 205, "question": "Are you not quietly encouraging this kind of behavior?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "No, I'm not quietly encouraging it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 208, "question": "I want one of those affairs Jackie Collins is writing about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 209, "answer": "They do.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jackie Collins"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "What's rude sex?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "Well, you don't want me to tell you on this show.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "Where are you going with this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "ORGAN: So, I know you weren't born four years before me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "How do you preserve yourself so brilliantly?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "I'm a one man band.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "Joan's big secret is she never goes to the sun, hasn't done since she's 21, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "She's in the sun all the time, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "You were in Saint-Tropez?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "Not recently, but the last time I was there, she was there.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Saint-Tropez"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "Were you like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "When I came to America, being English, I threw myself out on my pool every day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "What is the secret of continuing to write books that people buy in such huge numbers, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "WDT", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "I think it's because I write characters that they are interested in.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "What do you think having been through this now several times, what do you recommend to people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "Well, there's no best way to deal with it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "Are you still on the dating scene?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "I live my life like an affluent bachelor.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "VBG", "RP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "``", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 326, "question": "What does it mean?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "It means when I was a kid growing up, I would read my father's \"Playboy.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "No?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "I have a man for every occasion.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "How many occasions are we talking about here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "Oh, well, that would be revealing too much.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "What's been your overview of the male species?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "I think men are fantastic.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 352, "question": "Should women ever fully trust the man they're with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 353, "answer": "No, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "You're nice on this show, horrendous on the other show -- road to everybody, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "NN", "TO", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "Honest is what I'm afraid you're looking for.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "How many copies do you think shift to this world?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "I love that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "What is your Twitter address?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "JackieJCollins.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "CD", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 386, "question": "What is yours?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 387, "answer": "It's at @PiersMorgan.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "POS", "WRB", "."], "qSentId": 398, "question": "What do you think about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 399, "answer": "I write good sex, that's why.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "Gloria, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "I'm very well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "So, I suppose the obvious question for me is how's the back?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "Titanium reinforced.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RBR", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "And when they hit those, sort of, landmarks, that's scary, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", ",", "NN", "IN", ",", "NNS", ",", "IN", "POS", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "STEFAN: Well, that's where you see I'm going by, because I feel better than ever.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2004"]}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "CD", ":"], "qSentId": 445, "question": "Tell me about this new album because this is the first English speaking album in five years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 446, "answer": "No, actually, since 2004 --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "So, what was he like to work with -- same kind of thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "IN", ":", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "It's a big fun.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NN", ":", "RB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "How old were you at the time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "I was two year -- just under two years old when you came.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Bay of Pigs"]}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "You have no memory presumably of this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "I have memories of my father, his smell, the night he left, the day he came back from the Bay of Pigs.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Vietnam"]}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "How much of your huge success did he get to see?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "None, actually because when he came back from Vietnam, I was about 13 years old and he went downhill very fast.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 556, "question": "What do you think he would -- given that he obviously knew you were musical and anything else, what would he have made of what happen to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", ":", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 557, "answer": "STEFAN: I know what he would have made of it because a few years ago, I never listened to those tapes because it breaks my heart.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "Have you listened to any of them since?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "No, I can't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "What does it mean?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "Wepa means absolutely nothing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 585, "question": "Did you scream Wepa when President Obama became president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 586, "answer": "I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "What did you feel in that moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "It was transcendent.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 629, "question": "You told the world, you played in almost every country, in some stage, when you see what used to be called emerging countries, China, India, Brazil, and others, really becoming now very faster super powers in their own right, when you see that, are you excited for that potential or like many Americans -- do you feel slightly intimidated and threatened by that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "NNS", ",", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "JJR", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "JJ", "NNPS", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 630, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["China", "India", "Brazil"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 636, "question": "There's no point having a publicist anymore, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 637, "answer": "No, exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 652, "question": "Why Emilio?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 653, "answer": "OK, I will let you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 654, "question": "Why didn't the rest of us get a shot at it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 655, "answer": "You were far away.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 665, "question": "Only boyfriend you've ever had?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 666, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 676, "question": "How did you stay still chaste?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 677, "answer": "There were no male admirers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 708, "question": "How did priorities change after that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "NNS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 709, "answer": "Well, you know, our priority has always been our family.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "CC", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 720, "question": "When was the moment you walked again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 721, "answer": "Actually, I walked again in the hospital after they reconnected me -- but not by myself.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 728, "question": "That's true love, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 729, "answer": "Yes, it is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Cuba", "Miami"]}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 730, "question": "Do you dream wistfully of the day that Castro is gone and you can go back to Cuba?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 731, "answer": "Well, go back -- I don't think I could ever live in Cuba because my home is Miami.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Castro"], "LOCATION": ["Cuba"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Cuba"]}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "JJ", "NN", ",", "TO", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 734, "question": "Wouldn't you, for the sake of your father, wouldn't it be quite a moment for you to fly to Cuba post-Castro to complete really the job that he start?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 735, "answer": "Well, I tell you this, my dream both on a personal level and on a professional level -- professional level, to sing in a free Cuba, to share my music with my people.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Cuba"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBG", ",", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "DT", "JJR", "VBP", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 756, "question": "What does this all mean, \"The Tanning of America\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", ",", "``", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 757, "answer": "Well, tanning, I -- is a term I dubbed that represents the process of the next generation of kids that no longer see color when they see each other.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 760, "question": "How much of that is done through social networking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 761, "answer": "Well, I think social networking did a lot to help intensify the phenomenon.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Osama"]}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "NN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 769, "question": "-- what would you do?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 770, "answer": "I honestly think that he should speak to what he did with capturing Osama bin Laden.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 781, "question": "And, you know, I feel for the fact that he has these headwinds in front of him and you know the Republicans are doing a very good job of painting that picture, like what did he do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNPS", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 782, "answer": "Let's talk brands here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Beyonce"]}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 784, "question": "Which individuals out there right now do you think has a complete mastery of their brand and at the top of their game?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 785, "answer": "I think Beyonce.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 813, "question": "Why did his brand collapse?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 814, "answer": "You cannot lie to the media.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 825, "question": "Who are the smartest people you've worked with in terms of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 826, "answer": "Jay-Z.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", ":", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", ":", "PRP$", "JJS", "NN", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 840, "question": "But assuming he reads the book and he puts you in charge of rebranding him, remarketing \"America, PLC,\" \"America, Incorporated\" -- what would you do to get this country back on its feet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBG", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "VBG", "``", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "''", "``", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "''", ":", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 841, "answer": "I think we need to -- we don't have the -- our export, our cultural -- our biggest export was our culture, you know, our movies, our stars.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["PLC"], "LOCATION": ["America", "America"]}}]